In the daytime, I'm Marinette.
Just a normal girl, with a normal life.
But there's something
about me that no one knows yet.
Because I've got a secret.
♪Miraculous, simply the best♪
♪Up to the test when things go wrong♪
♪Miraculous, the luckiest♪
♪The power of love always so strong♪
♪Miraculous♪
"Conformation (The Last Day - Part 1)"
It's the first day of summer break in Paris!
Classes are barely over and the campaign
for the mayoral election has already begun!
Tourists have already started arriving from
all around the world to savor a taste of Paris...
...taking advantage of the good weather and making
great memories in the company of family and friends!
Good weather also prevails in London,
where Adrien Agreste and
Kagami Tsurugi arrived yesterday!
According to a statement from the Agreste brand, the couple
will be pursuing their successful modeling careers there.
A story by our correspondent in the UK.
.. right after this message.
For flawless skin and flushing out toxins...
Perfection, the drink that hydrates...
...to perfection!
Now that our children are safe in London,
we can launch the Perfect Alliance.
One day, they’ll understand that
we did this all for their own good.
Take care of the poison
while I prepare the remedy.
Nooroo, dark wings rise!
Dark wings fall!
Akumatize me, dear Megakuma!
Mullo, Kaalki, Orikko, your powers are now mine!
Sublimation!
I choose the power to fly.
Multitude!
Voyage!
After spreading bad dream
dust all across the world,
I awakened the dormant nightmares
in each human's mind...
Voyage!
Fall in!
The nightmare has begun...
...and our wish to bring our children
together can finally come true.
I want to see Adrien!
You'll have nothing more to do with my son.
We'll see about that!
I'm coming, Adrien!
Adrien!
I'm going to save you!
Mister Agreste?
Father!
Nooooo!
Why did you do that, Marinette?
ADRIEN!
I have to free him from the dragon-
I mean, from his father!
He's in London now, Marinette, remember?
What's happening?
Tikki, I need to find out where Mr.
Agreste has sent Adrien.
I need to free him—
I mean, to talk to him...
At least, make sure that he's okay!
♪Hey, this is Adrien's voicemail.
Leave a message.♪
What?
Just like the perfect couple, use Perfection,
the fragrance that'll suit you perfectly!
His father won't tell you a thing, will he?
He won't.
But maybe his assistant, Nathalie will...
Adrien told me that she was always kind to him.
Let's go and talk to her.
I have an errand to do... see you later...
Aren't you going to eat
something before you leave?
I'm not feeling very hungry, Dad!
It’s understandable you'd have a poor
appetite after Adrien's departure, honey...
...but breakfast is the
most important meal of the day!
No, no, no, don't worry...
...this has nothing to do with Adrien!
I'm fine, I promise!
Besides, he's just in London.
He's probably doing great,
there's no reason to worry!
I was just heading out
to meet up with my friends.
And that mountain of croissants
comes at a perfect time!
Love you both!
I've gotta tell you... I
had the most horrible nightmare.
Marinette was so sad that Adrien
was gone that she stopped eating.
And she became so teeny, teeny tiny...
...that a mouse gobbled her up!
I had a nightmare too.
You were so worried about Marinette
that you were akumatized into Werebaker.
You trapped Marinette inside a giant brioche...
...and an army of croissants
and macarons had to protect her.
Marinette!
I've gotta hide at your place!
Monarch is about to find me and
I'm terrified I'm gonna blab YOUR...
...your secret identity!
Oh no, it'll be even worse
if I hide at your place!
Are you okay, Alya?
Yeah!
It's just that we can't be seen together!
Aly—
Tikki. I can't think...!
I...
I just need to talk to Nathalie...
Once I know Adrien is fine, we’ll go see Alya!
It’s my fault...
I’ve destroyed everything...
Anticat,
there is only one way to repair all of this...
You’re going to give me Ladybug’s
Miraculous, and yours...
No!
Open the door now!
Let me out!
It's time to begin distribution
of the antidote to these nightmares.
The process has launched.
Open the door!
We all have nightmares.
We all have fears.
Unfortunately, these negative
emotions can lead to the worst.
After months of research, Tsurugi
labs have found the antidote.
The Perfect Alliance program
will allow you to find inner peace,
thanks to relaxing activities
proposed by Kagami and Adrien!
Whatever your level of anxiety,
you'll find serenity again with us.
To view your program for
free, say: Perfect Alliance.
This is insane! My father is out of control!
That is a pretty accurate
description of your father, yes!
What are you waiting for?
Transform and get out there.
Besides, we'll never find cheese here!
Plagg, hide!
There are cameras everywhere...
Relax!
May I remind you that kwamis cannot be filmed,
or have their voices recorded!
But my father could hear or see me.
.. transform into you-know-who!
There!
No cameras, no problem.
Tsurugi-san, could you activate
the camera on the robot in my son's room?
Shall we?
No, Plagg...
To watch your program for
free, say: Perfect Alliance.
I cannot transform...
What are you doing?
I’m not in my right mind.
I’m too angry; at myself, for
falling short of Marinette’s love.
At my father, for sending me here, in London.
At this stupid program and
these rings that use my image!
It makes me sick.
This nightmare is giving
me the horrible feeling that,
if I transform,
I’ll get akumatized and destroy
everything with my Cataclysm.
Marinette, Ladybug...
Surely Ladybug can help you...
But for that, I'd have to
reveal my secret identity to her.
And I can't.
We’ll see each other again, my friend,
I know it.
In the meantime, the only thing I can do.
.. is not get akumatized...
Perfect Alliance!
Adrien,
focus on the thing you like the most.
The soothing peaceful sound of the
foils brushing against one another...
The stimuli that Adrien's receiving on
his ring are relaxing his nervous system...
The images he’s watching are now
associated with a feeling of wellbeing.
He is forgetting all about the nightmares
he'd previously been obsessing about.
Soon, he'll calm down
and, later, fall sound asleep.
Perfect Alliance is a success, dear Tsurugi-San.
Marinette, wait!
You know that using your superpowers for
personal reasons has never brought you any luck!
It isn't personal this time!
It's for Adrien.
Tikki, spots on!
We all have nightmares.
We all have fears.
Unfortunately, these negative
emotions can lead to the worst.
After months of research, Tsurugi
labs have found the antidote.
The Perfect Alliance program
will allow you to find...
Ladybug and Cat Noir's
Miraculous are finally MINE.
At last, I can make MY wish.
Adrien, when I'm no longer here...
Your mother told me one day...
When your father hired me...
After months of research, Tsurugi
labs have found the antidote.
Oh, no...
He's going to do it.
That feeling when you're kneading dough...!
Making bread relaxes me so much...
See, Sabine?
I always told you that Adrien
would make a great baker.
Yes, you’re right Tom.
And Kagami is very gifted, too!
Adrien and Kagami really form a Perfect Alliance!
If I’d known it’d take so long, I would
have made myself a cheese sandwich for the voyage!
Drat. Where is she?
Marinette?
80% of the Alli@nce users
have already downloaded the app.
Good. Let's move on to the next phase.
I recommend that we wait until as many users as possible
are dependent on the antidote before we deprive them of it.
Otherwise, the shock won’t be great
enough to provoke the next phase of the plan.
Alya!
...as proven by our investigative journalism:
there isn't any problem
anywhere, is there Adrien?
Not a single one!
Everything's fine, Kagami!
Friends, I had an awful nightmare:
all the trees on earth had
been uprooted by extraterrestrials.
What if it was a prophetic dream?
What if the world is in danger?
Put this on, Mylene.
You'll feel better!
I refuse to touch an object that was made
without respect for the earth's resources.
Besides... these rings broadcast
bogus images of Kagami and Adrien!
Ivan? What's gotten into you?
I had a horrible nightmare that you were leaving me
to go take care of a polar bear whose habitat was threatened.
I'd never leave you. You're my teddy bear!
Come on, you can take that ring off...
No...
I'm sorry, I can't!
Hey! Wake up, People! That
thing's ot you all hypnotized!
The ring isn't our enemy, Mylene!
True, the program is lame, but Gabriel Agreste is like
us: he's just looking for a way to help Ladybug and Cat Noir...
It makes you chillax; you forget all about
your nightmares, your negative emotions...
...which means no more risk of being akumatized!
If this can really stop
Monarch from doing evil...
Kagami, how about a walk in the woods?
99% downloads.
We may begin, Gabriel.
Nooroo, dark-
Give me a minute...
What?
Emilie,
I have given up on everything.
My dreams, my ambitions, my morality...
...but I never gave up on you, my love.
I only have a few hours left now,
but nothing will stop me from seizing
Ladybug and Cat Noir’s Miraculous.
I will unite the magic jewels so I can
make the wish that will bring you back to me.
I can't let you do that.
If you make the wish to bring her back,
someone will have to go in her place.
Emilie would have never agreed to this.
Do you think I’d be monstrous
enough to sacrifice a human being?
This is terrible...
All these years working together,
and you really think that I’m a monster?
Nooroo, dark wings rise!
There’s nothing you can do to stop me now.
The tablet stolen from Master Fu?
It can't be.
Dark wings fall!
I knew that you would betray me, Nathalie.
I was prepared.
♪Cat Noir, Gabriel Agreste is Monarch.♪
♪I’m waiting for you at his place.♪
♪We’ll only have a shot
if we fight him together.♪
I knew it as soon as I realized that
you were instigating Adrien's defiance.
When you started insidiously supporting
his ridiculous fling with Marinette Dupain Cheng.
You’ll be loyal to me until the end, after all.
As for the rest, let bygones by bygones.
Just think of it as a horrible nightmare.
You can relax now.
Where is Adrien Agreste?
What have you done to him?
He is safe. But you aren't.
The whole world is in danger...
Monarch is about to send all of
humankind after you and Cat Noir...
He can't get hold of your Miraculous...
You don't look well.
I'll take you to the hospital.
I am beyond all medicine...
I used the Miraculous of the Peacock
while it was still damaged, and...
And soon I will...
Stop Monarch at all costs...
...that's what SHE would have wanted.
Transform back! Transform back!
What?
What did you say?
Wake up!
Nooroo, dark wings rise!
Proceed to the next phase of the plan.
So you two think you can do better than us?
You think your Perfect Alliance
is stronger against akumas...
...than Cat Noir and Ladybug?
Please, leave us alone!
Help! Please save us!
Oh no!
Mylene, I'm scared!
Don't be bemused, it's just the news!
Ladybug and Cat Noir have just abducted Adrien
Agreste and Kagami Tsurugi, the perfect couple.
There’s nothing left to protect
us from being akumatized, now!!!
Ladybug would never do that!
You saw what we all saw!
Trust me... We all know Ladybug!
Because she's saved each and
every one of us at least once!
We all owe something to Ladybug...
...and we know she would never kidnap anyone!
And neither would...
...Cat Noir?
I carefully held onto the Magical Charm that your
guardian Ladybug, had entrusted to Gabriel Agreste...
...unaware that he was me!
And the Cataclysm that your friend Cat Noir inflicted
on me won't have served only to destroy me, in the end!
The Cataclysm dust and the Magical Charm has
provided us Ladybug and Cat Noir's quantum imprint.
Such irony:
they've personally provided
me with the weapons to defeat them!
Transfer!
Hello, I am Gabriel Agreste,
designer of Alli@nce, and father to Adrien.
My son and his friend Kagami are
victims of Ladybug and Cat Noir...
If you want to help me save them, say...
...ALLIANCE, MIRACULIZE ME!
Alliance, miraculize me!
Take off your rings, it's a trap from Monarch!
He's found a way to take control of Alli@nce!
Ivan!
Join me, Mylene!
Let's find Ladybug and
Cat Noir and free our friends!
No, take off your ring!
Wait up, dude!
Where's Ladybug, and why
aren't you with Cat Noir?!
Precisely... would you agree
to be my temporary holder?
Doesn't feel like I really
have a choice here, do I?
Wait!
What if I get akumatized?
I know who Ladybug is...
I keep having this haunting nightmare
where I give the Miraculous to Monarch...
Besides... with Cat Noir's powers, I could...
I know: destroy the world, blahblahblah.
I'd better find Ladybug then, and quick.
I could help you if I still
had a phone to call Marinette.
Well alright, then:
it shall be Plagg alone
versus the rest of the world!
Pick up, please...
♪Voicemail, meow! Leave a message.♪
Cat Noir, I need you right now!
What in the...
Ladybug and Cat Noir quantum
imprint detector activated.
Ladybug's in there!
A Ladybug imprint has been
detected in your home, Gabriel!
She's probably trying to flee
from the Miraculized by hiding here.
How very ironic!
Ladybug!
Where are Kagami and Adrien?
Release them! Release them!
What?
Venom!
Clout!
Release Kagami and Adrien!
What on earth are you talking about?
Venom!
Release them!
Where are Kagami and Adrien?
You're trapped, Ladybug.
In a moment, your Miraculous will be mine.
I can't detect any imprint for Cat Noir.
She is alone.
That will make things even easier!
Where are Kagami and Adrien?
Release them!
Release Kagami and Adrien!
Ladybug, release them!
Ladybug detected!
Ah, there!
At least you can always count on
the villains to find the superheroes!
No!
Release them!
Transform back!
Of course...
Spots off!
Where did she go?
Where'd she go?
Where is she?
Ladybug is still here. I can feel it.
She must have transformed
back, she's vulnerable...
Make sure that the others
keep looking for Cat Noir.
I'm going to give a personal,
proper welcome to Ladybug.
After all, I am her host.
But before I meet her, you, nice kwamis,
are going to give me the powers to fight her.
.. and make me invulnerable!
Stompp, your power is now mine!
La-dy-bug!!!!!
I can't get hold of Cat Noir, or transform...
La-dy-bug!!!
Where are you?
Sorry.
Where's Cat Noir?
He fell victim to that wretched Alli@nce ring.
What are you doing here?!
This is where Monarch lives...
What?
Found you!
Marinette Dupain-Cheng?
No!
Tikki, Plagg, unify!
Call me: BugNoire!
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0